Albert Bonmassip Bové

Front-end developer

+34 610 28 11 95 abonmassip@gmail.com abonmassip.dev github.com/abonmassip

About me

I have been living abroad for 10 years, first in Zurich and then Los Angeles. I recently came back to Barcelona looking for new opportunities and challenges.

I am a front-end developer, experienced in JavaScript, HTML and CSS. I mainly use React and Next.js to build sites, and Three.js to create 3D experiences. I also have skills in back-end, I have used Node and Express, PostgreSQL and MongoDB. Because of my previous career in computer graphics as a <u>3D generalist</u>, I am also proficient in Adobe Photoshop, Blender and all aspects of 3D graphics.

Work experience

3D Generalist - Freelance

Los Angeles, USA (2021 - 2023)

I worked for various LA-based clients providing high detail architectural renders. The projects are mainly rental apartments and small businesses. I do all the modeling, texturing, lighting and rendering

3D Generalist - Multiwebdia Global Creativity

Zurich, Switzerland (2017 - 2018), Los Angeles, USA (2018, 2020)

Creation of logos, animations and media content for the European Final Four. I was in charge of modeling, texturing, lighting, animating and rendering.

3D Generalist - Soler&Palau

Zurich, Switzerland (2015 - 2016)

Production of Architectural Visualization renders to show ventilation system installations for domestic, commercial and industrial environments.

3D/2D Artist - EXON GROUP

Barcelona, Spain (2014 - 2015)

Creation of 3D environments, game-engine assets and interface elements for arcade machine games. My tasks involved modeling, image editing, texturing and animation.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Multimedia Studies - Polytechnic University of Catalonia Barcelona, Spain (2007 - 2011)